The history of paid soldiers is so old that some call the mercenary work "the second oldest profession in the world." Apparently, Ronan Falcon had already used them to unite tribes of people into one Falcon Empire. Sometimes paid warriors gained glory worthy of the heroes, and ballads were sung about their groups. In the Empire, mercenary became so popular that over time unconventional soldiers became regular warriors in many armies.