Mages of the Silver City, who have shown so much fascination with the Magic of Nature and the devotion of the Earth Dragon, received the title of Druids from the Forest Elves. For many generations, this function was reserved exclusively for the native inhabitants of Irollan, but the need to provide care also for forests far from the Elven kingdom limits prompted King Vanna to work with selected wizards, making them Guardians of the Forest.