Among the written works will be accounts of those who fought side by side with Living Saint against their enemies. However, you will not find the words of those who fought against these creatures. The simple reason - there are no such people. Living Saint were created not for mediation, but for fighting.Indeed, these Elrath servants are great evidence that even the most virtuous teachings need a few bloody servants if diplomacy proves not to be an effective way.